Anmol Singh Yadav

Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh, India



linkedin.com/in/anmol-singh-yadav-ab4063179



sanmol016@gmail.com

Summary

I am Anmol Singh Yadav, pursuing my B.Tech from Vellore Institute of Technology from Computer Science specialized in Cyber Security and Digital Forensic. I am a first year student. I am very interested in learning Hacking and Codings, I am trying to be perfect in it.

Experience



Application Developer

Police Department, Madhya Pradesh

May 2020 - May 2020 (1 month)

I have completed the internship with Madhya Pradesh Police under the Director-General of Police(DGP) Madhya Pradesh and my project coordinator. During this one month internship that was held from 1-May-2020 to 31-May-2020, I worked as an Application Developer. I was leading a team of four members through which we developed an Android Application - 'JanSahyog- App for Drivers'. I also did the Literature part of the project.

Education



Vellore Institute of Technology

B.Tech, Cyber/Computer Forensics and Counterterrorism

2019 - 2023

Doing my engineering in the field of Computer Science with specialization in Cyber Security and Digital Forensics.



Allahabad Public School, Allahabad

Computer Science

2015 - 2018

I had opted Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics and Computer Science in class 12. I had secured 83%

Licenses & Certifications



National Workshop on Competitive Coding - Coding Blocks



National Workshop on IOT and Cyber Security - Virtusa



Course on computer concepts (CCC) - NIELIT

GO1807022447



Advancements of Hybrid Intelligence and soft Computing - Machine Intelligence Research Labs (MIR Labs)



UiPath Academic Challenge 2019 - UiPath



Ethical Hacking Workshop - FLUXUS - IIT Indore 8671



The Complete 2020 Web Developer Master - Udemy

UC-bcd3121a-3b00-4a0b-a2d1-ff73d5ce0def

- Competitive Programming Problems Coding Blocks
 CBOL-85390-0946
- Introduction to Data Science in Python University of Michigan
- Autopsy Basics and Hands On (8-Hours) Basis Technology 8pczlul4fp
- Applied Plotting, Charting and Data Representation University of Michigan S3THNUMRVGGQ
- (m) Cybersecurity and the Internet of Things University System of Georgia
- Applied Machine Learning with Python University of Michigan
- **LFS216: Linux Security Fundamentals** The Linux Foundation

Skills

C (Programming Language) • C++ • Cybersecurity • Data Structures • Digital Forensics • Programming Languages • Hacking • SQL • Python (Programming Language) • SQL Injection